My dear fiancée.
How are you?
It's been a little over a month
since my life here at the
magic capital of Dirashik started.
I've finally gotten used to school life.
I've made a female friend, too.
To gain experience and become a
gentleman who is worthy of you,
I work hard every day.
Kunon.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Elia Hesson of Ability.
Can I interest you in our faction?
Why don't you join us?
Wow, she's sparkly and pretty and cute.
I've never seen anyone like her
in the countryside where I'm from.
My heart is starting to race.
I'm more interested in
you than the faction.
Would that be an impure reason to join?
Great, thank you.
People at school often tell me that
my idea of a gentleman is wrong.
What do you think, Your Highness?
FAIRIES CHECKING THE ANSWER
Conflict?
Right. Ability, Rationality, and Harmony.
These three factions used
to be in conflict.
Oh yeah?
Hey, do you think you can fly higher?
S-Sure.
Yes, let's keep you there.
They still get heated up
when it comes to magic,
but it seems they settled down
into more of a friendly rivalry.
I'm glad this is a peaceful time.
Recently, I'm having a lot of fun
doing experiments with you, Kunon.
Kunon Gurion.
She's gorgeous.
The girl from Ability
was also very cute, though.
I'm Elva Daglight from Harmony.
Would you like... to join us?
A lady who shines seductively
like polished obsidian.
I think she's still a teenager, but
her glamour is making me dizzy.
Why ask such a silly question?
Princess of the moonlight,
everything shall be as you wish.
What?!
It's a promise.
Your magical power is wavering.
If you want to fly long distances,
you need to learn to keep it stable.
Oh, sorry.
But Kunon! She was from Harmony!
What of it?
W-Wouldn't that be two-timing?!
Kunon, dear!
She's super cute!
Who the hell is he?
I'm Cassis of Rationality.
Will you join us, please?!
An exceptionally pretty
girl's exceptional smile!
I'm glad I came to the city.
Father, Mother, thank you!
What is up with this guy?
Please, Kunon?
You're starting to wobble
a lot out of nowhere.
You have to focus.
Huh?
L-Listen, Kunon. Would you like
to join Rationality?
Huh? Why would I?
What?
Riyah, why don't we finish up?
Huh? Whoa!
H-Hold on, Kunon!
This wasn't like you.
Of course two-timing isn't commendable,
and three-timing is even worse,
but a request from such a cute—
I would've agreed if a lady had asked.
What?! Then...?
I thought that was the
cutest of the three.
The city sure is something else.
Kunon.
Ah, the sleeping beauty
from the other day.
H-Hello, miss.
Hello. Riyah, I heard you're
joining Rationality.
It's good to have you.
Kunon, would you like to join?
Of course!
No gentleman would decline
an invitation from a lady.
If there is one, I'd do a
double take at his face.
Although I couldn't see it!
He agreed to join three factions?!
Yes.
They will not be happy if they find out!
Right. Even if things are peaceful now,
he can't do that, can he?
Cheers!
You did it, Elia!
As expected of the biggest
boy magnet of the faction.
A pretty girl even the goddess
of beauty would stare at!
Please stop that, Mr. Bael.
Nice going, pretty girl!
Even though a pretty girl with
a pure heart is fictional!
Go out with me, pretty girl!
No, go out with me!
You can cuss me out
and dump me on the first date!
I'd like to ask your hand for marriage!
Let's pay back a debt of
500 million necca together!
Celebrate more.
You've managed the difficult task
of securing a promising newcomer.
Mr. Bael!
Excuse me. I worked hard, too.
Yeah, good job! You did well, too.
Thank you very much—
Now Ability is in stable condition.
Please don't show up out
of nowhere, Mr. Genevis.
I'm sorry.
Great work.
He's actually a good guy, but the way
he talks is kind of annoying.
You did it.
Yeah. Cheers!
However... there's an unsettling rumor.
A rumor?
Damn you, Ability!
Well, if it isn't Rationality.
I wish you didn't barge
in without permission.
As always, the way you talk
pisses me off, Genevis!
I'm gonna kick your ass!
Ms. Sandra is as scary as usual.
So full of energy.
Is that because you had meat?
Huh?! Are you picking fight with me?!
He's not really a bad
person. Just annoying.
Did you need something, Lulu?
Yes, actually—
Like hell he needs something!
That uggo over there is spreading
bullshit that she succeeded
in recruiting Kunon,
so we came to complain!
What?! It's not bullshit!
And I'm not ugly!
Shut up, ugly!
Everyone is ugly except for me!
Learn to align your attitude
with your ugly mug!
Excuse me?!
Elia is a sweet girl!
That's right! A sweet girl in love!
I-I'm not in love.
Sweet? Oh, please! More like stinky feet—
Cassis, stop talking.
Or I can't speak.
Please excuse him, Elia.
He likes to tell the truth.
Oh, right.
Hm? That's not an apology, is it?
And what did you come here for?
We determined the order of
recruitment fair and square.
Yes. But there is an unsettling rumor,
so we came to check the answer.
A rumor?
Shilto should be heading here right now.
I am here.
As we agreed, we approached
Kunon Gurion in the order of
Ability, Harmony, and Rationality.
Yes, and that's why we—
He said yes to all three factions.
What?!
Technically, Ability
failed the initial approach,
but the second student succeeded.
I did.
Ugh!
Why not me?
This is unprecedented.
It seems... we've got someone
truly out of the box.
Is he serious, or is it all lies?
We'll just have to ask him directly.
The master of the forest!
Let's run, Princess Mirika!
No, we can't.
There's a village up ahead.
So I have to stop it right here!
Dear brother!
Prince Lyle!
You've got guts.
That's what I expect from the
vice captain of the Wild Bears.
Not at all.
I still have much to learn.
Coming back after the sun has set?
Where does she go out to?
Welcome back, Princess Mirika.
I'm home, Laura.
You received a missive from the senior
school for nobles about the final exam.
The time has come.
And another letter.
From Kunon?!
"My dear fiancée." Oh my!
So he's doing a lot of magic experiments.
A bacon-making experiment?
I see you still like bacon, Kunon.
Huh?!
Is everything okay?
He's made a female friend.
She must be his classmate.
Nothing to worry about.
R-Right, nothing to worry about.
Isn't that right, Kunon?
I'd like to start a
household account book.
What is that?
And why do you need my shopping memos?
Keeping precise records
of income and expenses
is the most important
thing in making money.
What do you do with the
money you make at school?
I chuck it into the drawer.
And the receipts?
You've bought stuff like seeds of
whatever and lots of meat, haven't you?
I don't have the receipts, but I
wrote down all income and expenses.
It's part of a noble's education.
I was told to keep good records.
That makes it easier!
Please give me those memos.
What?
Hmm, where did they go?
I piled stuff up too high in
my lab and it all fell down,
so I haven't touched it since.
Master Kunon!
Wow, scary!
Go through it and find them all, please!
R-Really?
I'm not good at organizing
and keeping things tidy.
Master Kunon! You'll be late for school.
Coming!
Good morning, Kunon.
Good morning.
Your voice is as beautiful as ever.
It's as if I can also hear the beautiful
voice in your beautiful heart.
Good morning.
Good morning, Miss Reyes.
That bacon...
Hide yourself, now!
Hank, that bacon!
I came up with the idea last night
and made it first thing this morning.
But whatever!
Now's not the time for that!
The seniors from the factions
are looking for you.
Me?
You saying yes to all the factions
has become a huge problem.
If they find you, who knows what—
I found you!
Come with me.
The representative is waiting.
Nice to meet you,
one who is passionate like the sun.
I'm happy to follow you anywhere.
Wait, are you mad?
A little.
If it's only a little, then no big deal.
Thank you for the food.
Mmm, tasty!
This is Hank's new bacon sandwich.
Would you like some, ladies?
No, thank you.
Finish it already.
How can he be so calm in this situation?
Today's smoked fish isn't too bad.
It doesn't make me nauseous,
and it's just salty enough.
Perhaps you should consider
smoking fish more often?
Business as usual over here, too.
Fish is tasty as well,
but the ocean is far from here,
so we don't get fresh fish often.
Apparently, sorcerers
who have traveled far
sometimes bring back frozen seafood
to make some pocket money.
Those are the only times you
can get fish around here.
Is that so? How unfortunate.
But do you think freshwater
fish can be farmed near here?
I wonder.
Maybe look for research
reports at the library?
Kunon, if I find the reports and it seems
it could be done, would you help me?
Never mind that. Please go now.
It'd be my pleasure!
How lucky am I to be
escorted by so many fairies?
Kunon.
W-Will he be okay?
Granted, I don't see how
he could be, though.
Did you see fairies somewhere?
Oh... That was a metaphor.
This is incredible.
I didn't know there was a castle
like this on the school grounds.
Shut up and walk.
If you'll escort me, I'll stay
quiet and follow you anywhere.
Then talk more.
He's here, representative!
Welcome. I am Bael Kirkington,
representative of Ability,
and we use this castle as a base.
Nice to meet you. I'm Kunon Gurion.
So these are representatives.
First, let me apologize.
I'm sorry for summoning you like this
when you don't belong to any faction yet.
I'm honored to have been invited.
Thank you for having me.
I think it's some massive creature,
but it's too big to really tell.
But I trust you know
why you were summoned?
My name is Lulomet, and I'm the
representative of Rationality.
Nice to meet you.
A dark tree like a shadow.
First time seeing a person with a plant.
I'm the representative of Harmony, Shilto.
Nice to meet you.
I've been wanting to meet you.
I hope you can make time to spend with me.
What?
Huh?
Hey, brat!
Do you realize the situation you're in?!
This is your fault!
Sandra.
Because of you, three factions
are about to get into a fight.
How are you going to settle this?!
Please don't fight over me.
Fish.
Water attribute?
I have a feeling we'll get along.
I'm sure the magic you use is wonderful.
Do you have time after this?
Would you like to talk about magic?
He's... crazy.
He indulges women and
is weak against women.
It's just as the report said...
No, it's more than that.
It seems it'll be faster
to speak to him via Shilto.
Me?
Questioned by you, I may tell
more than you ask.
How about we do this over some tea?
Let's do that. This might take a while.
Right.
Nice to meet you. I am Genevis.
Please feel free to call
me Geneva with affection.
N-Nice to meet you, Mr. Geneva.
An evil spirit. No, a human?
What's wrong?
Could it be my laughter?
Sorry. I just can't help it.
So which faction will you
choose at the end of the day?
Earlier... That was scarier than Rinko.
Which faction do you want to join?
Yours, of course!
That's what I wish I could say.
Which one?
Many ladies have recruited me,
but it's impossible for
me to choose just one.
Therefore...
I'm going to join all factions.
Huh?
What?
Next episode:
"The Unprecedented Troublemaker."
NEXT TIME: THE UNPRECEDENTED TROUBLEMAKER